So it's kind of hard to not have that.
Good morning.
Oh, I'll be home in a second.
I'm just walking home.
I started up on the streets.
It's such a beautiful day.
Look at that.
Hey, it was fun last night.
hi devil eyes i'm out and i'm out i'm actually not out and about i'm just like walking back
but i got my coffees
i got alcohol
cigars and a McGrittle
it's a breakfast of champion no fish tacos
Hey, maybe today, I don't know, I might go down to the beer, I might go down to the beer today, but I have to like look up the happy hours again.
I think it like a sort of like $5 fish tacos will sound pretty good, several hours.
I think I'm getting kind of like, you know, okay.
Hey, McDonald's a little bit.
I think I must have improved something about it because I used to be able to eat it like
If I ate it twice two days in a row
You hear that? I'm just glad I haven't turned into Ronald McDonald or one of his family members. I love McDonald's, I eat.
Hey, what's up homie? Hey, Preside. I'm almost there. I'm almost home.
This was like
Let me get on the stream.
Thank you!
Okay
Well, now I'm getting to the secret place, so I'll get it back, give me literally 30 seconds.
Derp my dog
What money
What money would that be you want it now I want to know oh my gosh
I'm a little bit back to my flannel
No, I'm not copying good times that like who in their right mind would like
Look at good times and say hey, I want that. I'm just kidding. Good time. I love you. Good time. Good time is a good guy
but
I was accused of, like, maybe pushing him off of YouTube
so I could steal his fashion sense and his...
I don't know. I don't know.
One-way network.
I don't even need to get into it.
Hey, there. I came to...
I mean...
Can you hear me?
I was not at a good show.
Like, a really good show. Yeah, we can hear me.
Howdy good, Joe. Hi, Trixie. Hi, good morning, Trixie.
Good morning.
Oh, you're eating my microphone and my bags.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's my camera.
What are you doing?
Are you purring?
You just purr? You come by?
You're in purr.
Hello.
No.
Hello, Trixie.
Okay.
So what money, white dog?
I want money now.
Just everybody just shower me with, you know,
everyone's saying, oh my god, Saige's all about money.
That's why he doesn't show me.
She has elephantitis?
Oh my god.
And now I feel bad.
Now I feel bad.
Are you serious?
That's why she got so upset when I made those jokes. You like Rudy?
Look at Rudy. He's watching at the
They're watching you're watching up there at the door
Hi good morning
We're down
She does oh my gosh, well, I'm sorry
No, we never know. That's the problem was like somebody that doesn't always have their
Their
Their camera on we don't know
What if the person we're making fun of and joking about has elephantitis and just imagine this
And then I feel like a real dick
Anyway, no, I don't I seriously I don't make I don't I don't make fun of
cool. Maybe it's karma? Yeah, but I do think you're born with it. There is karma. I mean,
it's a karma. I can explain karma and how I learned, you know, what we all hear about karma,
like karma's a bitch and blah, blah, blah. But there's, and what it means is like, you do good,
you get good, you do bad, you get bad.
Yeah, I mean that clearly goes more along the lines that what you put out in the universe can reflect back to you
I say karma is
Cause and effect and
Like and every cause has an effect and in fact we're like in this chain of cause and effects and
you know, oh
Devil eyes, you know, I bet it was like so cool yesterday like
Like, you know, it was just a little bit different like it was a different kind of day
Maybe it's cuz it's like
Just reached the grand the granny gang granny gang, but you know, I love my grandma
I mean, you know, she passed away several years ago. I
was telling my friend a story like I
Have
My grandma lived till she was 93 and she hated
getting old. It's okay. Now, my grandma hated getting old. She was a beautiful woman and
then she, you know, growing up, she and my grandfather, you know, they're in the same
house. They were pretty much natives of the city I live in now. They were both born here.
Right and they lived they lived here when there was a train station here and stuff
And it's like there's not even any route. Maybe there's artifacts of that might be some kind of artifacts of the train station
There's interesting things all around here. There's also every Dondo. There's something called
Moonstone Beach. That's what it was originally called the city Moonstone Beach
you know and
There's a picture you could actually go
On the beach and
Moonstones would just be copiously washing up. There is like this huge
Supply of Moonstones. I'll show you what it looks like
Well, this is just like kind of this is kind of one of those pictures like I'm
From like the
1800s, I'll tell you a little bit about what is it saying Wikipedia?
It wasn't a new it might have been a new just notice and there's one in Cambria, California, but this is a
Redondo was called moonstone beach. Actually the streets here are named after
Either the daughters of these I think Spanish can kiss the doors on one side and then on the other side. There's
Here's the moonstone beach. This is a pig and look how imagine like living in these days how old-fashioned and wonderful it was look at this
You know, they're just and they'd go why is it can you imagine wearing that to the beach?
Like full I mean
It's all I mean, I think Muslim like, you know certain very strict religious Muslims are less
Overdressed than these people going to the beach
I mean, it's full of heavy skirts and hats.
I mean, it's crazy, but yeah, they'd go and collect.
That's the pier right there.
You can see the pier.
The pier burned down once, but they rebuilt it, right?
But that's the pier.
Now this beach is not there anymore.
They basically dug it up to, you know,
make a foundation for the power plant.
And so there's no more beautiful moon stones.
I'm gonna wash you up on the shore that you can collect them.
I mean, that would probably be, if it was still there,
I would probably be a Moonstone salesman to this day.
Cause then I could just go pick up the rocks
and I could just sell them on Etsy.
I would have a wonderful business,
but now unfortunately there's no Moonstone.
I don't know where, like I would figure they would like
wash up somewhere else or like,
did they just like the Moonstones just stop coming?
I get a little bit confused.
Oh, there's Lola. Hi, Lola.
Come up here.
Here.
Come here.
Oh, Miss Lola.
Oh, there's Lola.
How are the kitty cats doing?
Yeah, so there's a little bit,
I mean, it looks like there was some,
a little bit of romance maybe
happening last night.
A little bit, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't
I would be jealous if I was in love with him,
but actually all I want is people to be happy, so.
If anyone's, if they're happy, I'm happy.
And I think actually, I think women are like really good
for men, like I think, you know,
they're kind of made for each other,
not no pun intended in a certain way.
Me, I don't know. I think I'm meant to be alone or something like that
But I think
Women can
Help, you know, raise them up turn them into real men and stuff like that's what maybe that's why I had a girlfriend at one point
But um, it was pretty it's cool. It was cool
But yeah, I had a fun night last night. I mean other than Tommy James coming up
Well, I still, you know, remember the day before, you're so...
Well, I was cordial, but, you know, I just said you're a terrible person.
I do have Squidward.
Peter, are you trying to make me cry?
That's not very nice. Easy, what's up?
Yeah, I mean, no, I do love Squidward.
That little, that motherfucker.
The Squidward's cute.
It's cute.
Yeah, he's cute, but, uh, what's it come up?
Someone come up and talk to me.
Let's have a talk today.
Kate, did you see last night's show at all?
I was wearing a nice white shirt.
I mean, I woke up, I should have combed my hair or something, I'll put my hair back
again.
Now it's a little, I'm a little bit, hey, quack, quack easy.
There we go.
Let me fix my hair.
You like his beetle haircut?
I do too.
Think you're destined to be alone too well
Like you know what song always goes through my head about me. It's like do you think you're better off alone and I'm like, yes
I think so. I think I probably am. I have a hard time trusting people and
I
Get bored easily, but at the same time, I don't I don't you know like to I hope that that hot bodybuilder
You missed last night? You went to bed early? Well, let's just say it was a pretty fun night.
We had a hyperactive or something, hyperconjurated hyperborian or something on who's like, you know,
really interesting.
You know, he's been a freemason, a golden dawn, and all these occult societies, and he's very smart and knowledgeable.
And we had some good debates. Pave tried to give Sig a tarot reading.
I think between both of us, we've attempted to read tarot for him, like maybe 20 times.
Then he starts going, you're shuffling wrong.
Terrible.
He asked for the reading or something.
And then it's like, he just starts to insult us.
And so I kicked him off.
I started to ban him.
He came on up on literally.
We came up literally like 50 times when I kept kicking him out and then he started taking over the whole panel
So he was an all seven of the panel things with his boyfriend 300 pounds or me through her glow
behind him going like this and
like in like just say
Making these bases and stuff and I think and it was like so weird
I don't know if that he was in the room with him or something like that, but it was like a psychedelic nightmare
Did I see the dear John video?
Is that from the 80s TV show dear John dear John
The time you read this note. I'll be gone. Oh, no
What about the dear John video? Who's whose video is the dear John video? It's not about me. Is it?
Hope please don't say it's about me and who who made it. Tell me about it
He told Paige that he was pro shit. She was just proof. Oh, I know. He's like, oh, yeah, you're just profile
No, no, and well, that's why I kind of like to do
Readings like for I don't like to do them for myself because I'm too biased of myself. Oh
She did
Because that's interesting because I remember I don't know. I'll just say that's a
Hold on. I have to go watch it right now. I have to go watch it, but you know
Also my name. Oh, let me go watch it
But let me put I have to put on a different video for you because I can't really
Share any of her stuff, but you guys can check it out, too. But I mean
Can't
You know, she's just known to be like this like, you know
Kind of a crazy person so I'm just gonna be careful with what I should I can't really I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I shouldn't shut up. You're talking about am yeah am
Am is I mean am means allied master computer. I think it's like AMC allied master computer, and then there's am she's just
Allied mistress or something. I'm not sure but she's she's allied with somebody hopefully not stroke off. I
Know they cancel there's there's no boarding trip. Okay. Well, she's making now AI videos and me and stuff
I mean, it's like you know at this point
It's getting a little silly
But let's have a look at
Here just give me a minute. I'll be right back. I didn't you guys need to check out what video she's showing
But I'm not gonna leave you under and entertained while I go so
I'm gonna literally put on a two-minute something for you
Just you just hang tight here, and I'll I want to give you my reaction to it because I haven't seen it
People were saying that last night dear John, you know dear John letter is like when you leave somebody
You just leave him a letter. It's a dear John, you know
I'm leaving you and stuff.
The relationship didn't work out.
And, you know, hopefully I didn't steal your wallet
on the way out, you know?
Yeah, you're, okay, let me see.
I mean, where is, I don't understand, why isn't,
oh, it's just custom, okay, let me see.
And pages gifted.
I'm gifted too. I mean, it's like I think everyone's gifted. Everyone has their own gifts
I mean, it's like she did a pretty like chilling
Chilling
Channeling of my friend Danny stranger and stuff and for a few other people and I think she's very talented in this in this
talking to the dead I
Feel I can feel the dead but like a lot of the dead
like you know
I'm not surprised Danny wanted to go straight to her and like not and talk to her instead
of me.
It's just like Benny.
Benny wants to go talk to Paige.
No one wants to talk to me.
I am not as beautiful and you know bubbly and vivacious and Canadian.
I don't know.
I don't know what it is, but you know, yeah.
Um, just give me a minute guys and I'll be right back. I just want to see what's being said
Okay, should I play I'll flick something for you on the way
Oh, let's call revelation of the method. Enjoy this one right back. I'm just gonna check out this video. Thank you so much
Hold on, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
I don't, I can't, I can't look at it.
But I saw it just disturb me
more than anything I've ever seen in my life.
That's the dear John letter you're talking about.
I mean, the dear John, did everyone just leave?
I mean, I literally, that was like a fake out.
But do you know what I just saw?
You know what I saw
Who saw who's seen it tell me guys describe what it describe what you see. I don't know I don't know if like I'm seeing the right thing
I'm in shock though. I'm absolutely disgusted. Oh
You're giving me kisses. Okay guys, you know what I just saw
You know what this her short is
It's the most disgusting fucking thing I've seen in my life.
It says, when hate bonding, hey Brandon,
it says when hate bonding, this is by AM, right?
We know who AM is, right?
If you don't know, you have to wake up pretty early
in the morning to fool me, or in the AM to fool me, right?
It means morning time.
But it also means darkness.
But okay, so, do you know what I just saw?
It said, it was a short, I saw myself,
I saw Tommy James, I didn't see any shirts on us and it said, I saw, I saw his kissing
and stuff, like actually like making love maybe, and it said, when hate bonding turns
into LGBTQ love.
I mean, I already saw the picture wasn't the picture bad enough. Like why do you have to bring like did you have to animate as making love?
Okay, here's what I'll say. There's Mary. I didn't watch it. I can't watch it. Maybe I have I think I
Had need to watch an empty stomach. I don't want to throw up, but um
First of all, I'm quite happy because I'm gay anyway, I wouldn't sleep with Tommy James, but
I think Tommy James really hates me.
It's sort of the fact that...
Hey, Alexandra?
Okay, I think she gets it now. She gets it now.
Maybe I'm not discussing it. Okay, babe.
Listen, can I hate Pond with Alexander?
Can I hate Pond back with you over Tommy James
and be friends with you again?
And then we can just go after him together.
And, hey, think about putting our AI skills together.
You and me.
Am.
This is you and me now.
Look at me in the eyes.
Okay?
Am.
What if we put our skills together to go after Tommy Jean?
Oh, he's horrible.
He said, I think you are a terrible person.
That's what he said to me last night.
All right.
What did I do to him?
Well, I'm not the greatest person ever ever ever to walk the earth. I
Mean there's people bet like a lot of people better. Am I the worst my terrible person?
Am I like, you know
What I mean, what like what terrible person to me is like, you know
Kind of murderers rapists, you know, just like, you know
Not just like
Somebody like that has dirty fingernails and stuff. You saw that short. You just saw the short. Yeah, do you see it right now?
It's Tommy James, and I'm making love and I see and she would always keep saying that I'm straight and stuff
She finally gets that I'm actually gay. So there's no other okay
You kind of you don't have to worry about sexual tension
Am okay, you don't have to worry about sexual tension between us and I always liked you
I still and I'm giving person and stuff. Oh
And look it. I do have a boyfriend my boyfriend's back and you're gonna be in trouble
Sup
Did you hear, someone got a video about Tommy James and I making love.
It's not real, it's not real, baby, it's not real, it's never happened.
Where are you?
I'm about to get to the end of this video next, but it's late, it's a little long.
Hold on, hold on, I'll fix it, I'll fix it, Squeety, hold on.
You got it?
Thank you.
Yeah, I'm you
Where are you?
It's an old man.
Heard music.
It's relaxing.
There's like a weird thing over there.
I think it's like a carnival.
That they're going over.
What is a carnival?
I don't know what that is.
I think it is possibly a carnival.
It looks like a circus in the middle of nowhere.
I think that's a magical circus.
You have to go.
Is it Vegas?
Yeah.
And what if, what if we went to the circus with you?
Well, but we're there, but it's a haunted house.
It's not even like,
when this is really not over, it's a circus.
What?
I think it is a circus.
Okay.
It is a circus.
Have you seen the house around?
What?
I think I do see a bunch of clowns walking around the park.
Can you find a clown tantrum?
I will.
Yeah.
Can you go but can you get closer to it? I want to see like like maybe like
I want to see them.
It's not open yet.
Okay but I want to get as close as you can.
All right.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
I mean, it's like, I think if I ever, like, you know,
it was like, you know,
the sound of it, so soothing.
It's a soothing sound.
I love that the sound is just,
that's what I love the most right now,
right here.
It sounds like, almost two-way up, so.
I don't know, like,
it's kind of like,
Is there water you can walk on?
I think there's water.
There's a lot of water out here.
I love this.
Guys, we're doing some IRL with my boyfriend.
He's going to squinty poop.
We're looking at him.
We're trying to put in something.
I already see clouds.
Can you see those people?
Yeah, those are clouds.
Can you talk to them?
No, I'm not going to bother them.
I'm going to bother them.
I like to bother everybody when I have my own, I can't.
Hey, hey, you're on YouTube, live on the side, it's like he...
Let's see if we see turtles.
I think we could see some turtles out here.
Look at that.
This is the best day ever.
Turtles?
I think it is.
We found a circus in the middle of nowhere.
And a turtle pond.
Where are those turtles?
Even though they're Pennywise as well.
Look if you can find Pennywise.
There's a circus and there's a sewer.
So it's perfect Matt
Everyone should just go outside
Look at the beautiful nature, what is that down here?
Is that a turtle?
Do you see how good to see the turtles right now?
Oh, there's a turtle.
Oh my gosh, a turtle!
Is that a duck?
There's ducks, there's ducks!
What kind of bird are those?
Oh shit, yeah, turtles, stuff.
A puffing?
Maybe it's like a penguin?
Well, it's like a lake.
Like a...
What's the baby turtle?
Hey.
I think there's ninja turtles down there because there's a sewer nearby.
The bird.
The bird is a really dark bird.
This is a sign.
The bird is a dark bird.
Because you know, I just pointed at the clackers gang.
I'm affiliated with the gang finally.
I was trying not to drill the hole.
I was just gripping it.
I was gripping the hole.
Perfect.
It's filming you like touch your feet like before your finger and then you like like this.
I have this turtle right here.
Is that a turtle?
Those are a duck patch.
They're gonna put a full speed.
If your feet stay down, you have to first swim.
Go first swim, it's cold dude.
Fucking cold outside
Imagine going for a swim
Yeah
No, give me a hundred books
Okay guys, is someone that sends me a hundred dollars no no no no no no no no fuck no
I'll give you 10 bucks out of it 200
Then I'll get arrested
Probably
Is it are you wearing tidy whiteies or box?
Both
Box of briefs or
Box of briefs
Yeah, I'm wearing boxer boots.
What color are they?
Look at that guy. He's running away from you.
I scared him. I scared him away.
Don't scare the kid.
Yeah, he's running because I scared him away.
I know, I know.
He's running away from Squidward.
You wouldn't do that.
I'm running, I'm telling you I'd run towards you and kick this.
Squidward is crazy.
Look who I'm dating guys, I'm dating Teletubbies, I'm dating Teletubbies people.
Let's go to the Carnival guys.
Why does he look why does that pickle look so sad
Yeah!
How'd you know?
There's geese!
Hong Kong!
They're buried also, they don't, like, kick your ass.
No, they're not, they're not running, they're coming towards you.
We won't get attacked by it.
They're buried down, smiling.
You need mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo-mo.
You're like one with the animals they don't run away from when I go outside
They're laughing at you are they laughing at you
One of it's injured look at the one of the geese
That's one leg
I think it's injured
I'm doxing whoever knows this place knows
I think my best, most interesting boyfriend, I think, in the world.
River, do you want to come move in with me?
Yeah, when the end of the world happens.
The end of the world?
Can I move in?
Make a bunker?
Revelation 17.
What does that say again, the death horse or something?
Oh, that's the one that one's about the harlot. I'll read it to you. I don't I kind of like don't know if I uh, I forget about
Like how they go
17 says
It's pretty spooky. It says
um, it says, um
After I heard this after I was sounding like a roar of a great multitude in heaven shouting
hallelujah
salvation and glory and power belong to our God
The end of the world is having to move in Squidward
You heard the song by the R.E.M.
It's the end of the world as we know it.
And I feel fine.
You heard that song?
And I feel fine, and I feel fine.
And I feel fine.
Yeah, it's a great song.
So, is that one of, yes, Guidi's in the,
how'd you know he's in Nevada?
There's, Lace Perks has figured out your state.
I'm sorry, she's docked to you.
Lace Perks.
Don't talk to my boyfriend
He's in Nevada. I think he's in Vegas or something but he found like the circus is actually in the middle of nowhere
It looks like I don't see a ribbon a road. I see some clowns walking around outside. I see we've seen ducks
We've seen turtles. We've seen geese
American Circus Alliance tent. That's what it's called. Oh, yeah
That's me in the corner, that's me in the spotlight, losing my religion, trying to keep a eye on you, and I don't know if I can do it, oh no, I said too much, I said enough.
I thought that I heard key slapping at my boyfriend's
squiddy poo.
That's my song I made.
This place is so big.
Look at that tree.
What a beautiful tree.
It looks like a pitchfork.
Is that called a devil's tree?
Can you climb that tree like Michael Jackson and go, yeah.
You can put on your camera and climb it as much as you can
I want to see I want to see what your butt looks like climbing a tree. It's the Joshua tree
It is a nice part, I mean, it's like I mean it looks like a sewer kind of but the trees are beautiful
I like the the wildlife. I want to see it. Look at Lenore
Look at mine. Here's my nature
The nature of a black cat
But anyway guys don't I think I told everyone I said, oh, I'm gonna go look at this video
It's called like it was called dear John and all I saw was like
It looks like a video someone someone captured of me having sex with Tommy James
Now that's upsetting a little bit. I don't because I don't remember that happening
So I feel violated
Not only by someone videotaping it but by having sex with Tommy James
I wouldn't do that.
Doesn't she remember I'm straight?
My whole gay act is all a big facade to attract women.
It's never worked once, but oh, there's a noise outside.
It's never worked.
Somehow, it's just been the worst idea I think I've ever had.
So I'm just going to go back to being straight,
except for Squidward.
I'll say I'm bye now.
Are you gonna give me a kiss?
Have a kiss?
If it may have kisses.
Kisses, kisses.
I'm gonna help me kiss your ear.
Good morning, brah.
Things are looking up.
Aren't they looking up?
We have thing that is.
We have things are looking up.
We have thing that might've been.
We have thing that once was.
We have thing that could be.
There's so many, and we have like that.
There's so many things around.
Oh, Rudy. Rudy's back. Hey, Rudy. Coming back. Oh, we see you. We see you. Don't try to hide. We see you peeking back behind me. We see you.
Yeah. Good morning, bruh. I love having bruhs now. I never really, I mean, I have brothers, but it's like, I never had like guy friends that I could call bruh.
Now I'm friends, or I'm dating Squidifu. And this is like, my dream come true, actually, because I can call my boyfriend bruh. He's like a bruh.
Now who are your who are your friends with you? You know anybody besides Chris K in the community. I'm squeety-foo. Who's your favorite?
Are you singing I hear I'm singing
He's gonna climb the tree guys, I think yeah, I know guys. Thank you
I want to get me. Hey, you know we can get married in Vegas. Is there an Elvis impersonator around that has a marriage license?
I'll be right there
You know what he's gonna say when we pay him he's gonna say thank you very much
Thank you things are looking up I know things are looking up
That's an elm tree. Hey, is this a nightmare and on the elm tree?
Wow, I'm full of great jokes today. Yeah, let me fix my hair
Do you like me with my hair down or my hair tied back?
Which one do you prefer?
Or would you prefer me tied up?
Like long hair well, I have a man bun there we go. It is a nice elm tree
Yeah, I would have be afraid if he actually climbed it. It would break
All the wind
Now why why do I hear the wind on the camera microphone, but I don't hear the wind
Rustling through the tree leaves, isn't it?
Okay
Best day of my life
I want to get married into that tree. Can you remember where that is so we can get married there?
I'll hire the Elvis impersonator you pay for everything else
Deal
Hello
Okay, you're back. Okay, thank God. Yeah
Okay. Well, it looks like, you know, why is everyone leaving? They're not happy for my
that I found love. Oh, okay, people are coming in. Guys, we're live on the scene. Hey, chicken
cakes, chicken cakes. We just saw geese and turtles and a circus tent and he touched grass.
I know I can barely hear
and nor can we see him.
I don't like looking at that depressed cucumber.
What's that drink he has?
Is he having more alcohol?
Is that a shrimp cocktail?
What is he having?
What's in that glass next to him?
Hey guys, I don't know, you know, but there's a really embarrassing video that was caught of
me
Making love. I think that's a
I'm 90% sure it's AI who are my love with today. This is my boyfriend squitty poo
Look at all the geese. Yeah, look at the geese. We're doing some IRL with doing some geese watching
I love it birdwatching. We're watching some keys and they make a beautiful noise
What if this this guy right here's like are you in a car? Huh?
J dogs here. He's back
Psyche what's up homie? How you doing man? You know my boyfriend squid?
That's your boyfriend. No squid. You got a boyfriend Psyche. Yeah
What's up J dog was cracking homie was popping
It's chillin chillin chillin
Yeah, it's a Friday man. It's another good Friday. Hell. Yeah, we don't make it
Friday I'm looking at some geese with my boyfriend
Um, yeah, we're having a great day. You know, like this is like an anti-dipressant touching your house
Really, thank you. Thank you. Did you see I don't know if you were paying to get Beatles live right now
Did you see thing that is was crying?
Sandman made thing that is cry and run off beat us panel because he was saying oh look at you were talking so much shit
on psyches about beta, oh, beta's this, beta's not.
Now look at Keith, you over here back on beta's panel
and now look at Keith and he ran thing that is off.
I don't know why I think that is ran.
He should have just, you know, fought him back
and then he was crying.
Wow.
It's thing that I think, I think he changed his name
and ran back over here.
Cause it says things are looking up.
Okay, well then well then he upgraded then that's what he did he upgrade. Hell yeah
I think I tried my final time with beta like we finally got the five minutes one-on-one
You know interview with it or talk that I've been wanting
It was just you two you just us. Okay. They're just us like me or like I was like, hey
Forgive each other say we both we both were different people and you know, and it's like, you know, even if it's like
drama on panels and stuff you can like like be friendly on the scene and it's like
No, I'm a piece of garbage and you know, what the heck even after all that dude
You can even after you pour your heart out and say you know what next but we both get each other wrong by gun be by gun
Let's just move forward
You know continue with the script, but you know be cool behind the scenes like
Yeah, it'll create ratings on both sides like it'll benefit both you guys
I mean, it's like I don't understand. I mean, I don't think logically either. I'm very right-brained and I have a very abstract mind
But it's like I have some kind of logic
You see the bigger picture though. That's the gif is between you and her you see like hey
We can make something out of this and sked of you know, why does this have to be this way? You don't have to
You don't hate her. I know you don't hate anybody. She hates she has so much hate and anger towards you and animosity
It's like not it. It's almost like an ex-girlfriend boyfriend type of you know, hatred, you know
Yeah, yeah, and the other person am I know, you know am it's
You know what I'm talking about well
She will I'm like dehumanized basically by her like she'll she mentions everybody else's name
Oh, and like, you know, she'll mention their names. I'm just the fraudulent psychic
You know, hey, ponder. I mean she just like uses these just
Yeah, I think we'll be on rumble actually
her show because she deletes her lives and so I can just be like just be with a rumble and stuff.
Yeah, yeah. I'm not gonna eat you. I'm not gonna eat your life, but it's like I don't know.
Yeah, but you don't want to risk it though because you know how she is. Bita is petty like that.
She'll try to strike your channel. She'll pull that bullshit.
There's no copyright because it's not. She deletes the lives, so it's not even like.
Yeah, she has no video to counter claim it. Yeah, I hear you man.
I don't know. I think I'll just like leave her alone. I mean, it's like, I don't know. It's just so silly, but yeah.
Well, dude, it's been what? Almost what? Since last May? Last April, May? It's gonna be a year, dude.
No, we're here. Like, that she's been like, you know...
That she flipped out.
I knew her since like November December the year before so it's like yeah 24 that was 2024. Yeah, I remember that
But how's that be better you're not feeling too well. Oh, yeah, yeah, dude. I had that
human meta something
It's like that new thing that came out
Where there's no cure for it. It leaves you all congested. It gives you like a pneumonia almost like in your body like a walking pneumonia
And like a boot and fuck me up for like two three weeks
Like it was horrible. I had to go to the doctor get antibiotics and shit
Oh, yeah, yeah, I'm a lot better now
Oh
I'm gonna be put our gene
Or what yeah, I'm having sex with Tommy James in your new short. So here he comes
What the heck?
Hey, what's up? Yo, what's popping?
So, what's what's going on? What happened with court and all that? Oh, I can't speak on anything about any of that
Why were you looking for Tony? I think is a better question on all honesty. Um, his name got brought up in something that that's why
Oh, yeah, yeah, and I what it was very important that I talked to him and I like a co-defendant. I
Can't really say because I don't want to get you know get myself in trouble or get anybody else in trouble, but
Okay, okay, let me put a number in the back and then you guys think I'm gonna put my text now number back there hold up
Okay
maybe it's like, oh, this will be uncovered soon.
But Archie, did you see the Tommy James and Psyche Sex?
Okay, let me come back, because I've got to grab my number,
and I'll come back, and I'll grab it back in the chat, hold on.
What was that like?
Did you know that there's a Tommy James
and Psyche Sex video out?
That's not true.
Go to the, go to the, go to the,
Oh, oh, fucking Alex being crazy again, yeah.
I did see she did a video about you yesterday gassing you up, and I hope you didn't fall for it
I haven't watched it, but I just saw that
It's awesome that said hate bonding leads to LGBTQ love and then I saw me and Tommy James in the good coitus
You know that right Alex. She's fucking insane
I mean she's gonna try to suck you back in again, right? Just so she could fuck with you all over again
I'm just telling you what it happened
I'm so happy with the publicity. I mean it's like I've been I mean you're not hearing a word. I'm saying
But did you see the sex tape though are you to see the sex tape though go to that and go to their shorts real quick
All right. Oh, I actually do it on my phone. Okay
IRL news time, I think, is the channel, and it's under the shorts.
And I haven't watched it.
I just have the picture.
Can you just play it and describe what you're seeing, because I can't play it on my show.
Why can't you?
Oh, whatever.
I guess she's a striker.
She is a striker.
But that doesn't matter you could just fight it you could play whatever
Can you think a video with me in it and my boyfriend or my not my boyfriend the Tommy James
It is a video of Tommy James and me having sex you think I don't see any shorts on this channel
Let me see if I can find it
Oh, it's an IPT wiki dot info shorts
I kind of got scared for a second. That was going to run me off.
You're crazy.
I had to jump, bro. I was like, what the fuck?
Yeah, it's kind of weird.
My steward is a little bit, yeah.
Oh.
That's so weird.
I'm having a video cam.
You're telling me to leave?
No, no, no. Don't leave. I'm just going to mute you.
New Yorkies.
Okay. Go ahead, RG. Do you see it?
Yeah, I'm looking at it right now. This is what hey body leads
Press me off the block
What do you see in black RG
No, I just I did yeah, it shows you and Tommy in bed together holding hands with a camera there
Yeah, Alex is a fucking
Whack-a-doo. She's a crazy person twice, but I
fortunately
Like I'm kind of immune to snake snake bites
Hey, then there's you french fries or the bald head
Why do you mean making me bald are you very bald not just bald looking very Syrax is
I just got pressed off the block by a goose.
A goose.
Yeah, it's totally like it swings all aggressively.
It was the alpha goose.
Alright, I'm going to jump it in the back.
Bye.
That most kind of scary
Wow so did you see the video Tommy or J dog oh
Which video it's go to ip2 wiki.info and look at the shorts real quick and look at the latest short
Okay, I'll be back. Hold on.
Shout out to RG for the mustache ride. Did you give someone a woman named Lace Perks a ride on your mustache RG?
Did you notice how I said women?
That's how much respect I have for you. I'm not gonna like, you know tease you
RG
I don't know who that person is either.
Let me look at the flashlights.
Let's see a beautiful woman.
Let me check out the picture.
I'm sure it is.
Oh, it's a guy.
It's a guy.
Oh, there you go.
RG is not gay.
It's a guy.
The guy's kind of cute.
He's in a hoodie and stuff.
I'm into guys in hoodies.
Today I was at McDonald's and there was a guy.
He was really cute.
I think he was gay because he was with another guy
and he had a shirt and said bully.
I thought you were with, what's his name?
Alex McQueen.
No, I'm with Squidward, but you know, but I don't think Squidward's word is a is it is it gay?
You did yeah, are you Alex gonna be upset? He's full-blown in love with you, I think
Well, you know there's room in my bed for one more. It's a big queen-size bed that this I bet you that's smelly
You know why it's not smelly is because I really bought a new mattress like a couple
of years ago.
It's not smelly because I bought a new mattress and then I
I slept in like three times literally because I just assumed you sleep on that food done
I do and so that's why the mattress is like perfectly clean. Like she
Alex was smelly is what I meant. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, I'm not taking a shot to you. I don't want to get sued. So I mean
No, Alex McQueen not my I know my ears is smelly. I'm in McQueen. I don't know if Alex McQueen is smelly
I just I just he's obviously in love with you
Well, I think you turned up gay. I'm pretty like irresistible Archie
All right, dude. I is that is that supposed to be you and Tommy James or is that good times a little more like good times
Yeah
What happened I think it's sirex and Tommy James. Yeah, it looks more like sire. I do like
That don't look nothing like you like
Psyche Cyrax as in like a Psy
It's the drunk English
Hey that RG Natty
She's sick
Are you sick Natalie what are you eating?
I saw I was watching one of your streams once Natalie and like a fucking I don't know what it was
But some type of bug was on your table. I saw you take one of your titties and smash the bug right on your table
It was one of the funniest things that ever seen in my life
You just smashed that bug with a titty
hilarious
It was really funny you be killing bugs with your titties
Okay, well, let me see what's going on. I mean, I'm gonna share my screen. I'm gonna see what's going on
I'd be this right now. Okay thing that is these problem, but I'm gonna share my screen. I'm just gonna put it on my screen. I don't come
Hopefully yeah, I won't probably gotta go see a lot of things. I guess this is fair use. Um, this is fair use and
Okay, let's see
You're pressing on him and I want to see your say
Okay, perfect. Oh my god, you see it. Yeah, yeah, let's see it. Let's see what's going on over at Peter's
Here we go.
There was a store. It's apparently there's something about some you heal card. Somebody won it and there was a big investment.
It is collectible. It is collectible.
Man, they were knocking each other out. It was bizarre.
Ain't no sex is not worth it. Oh, you know what? I mean they were punching each other. You know, we hang around doctors
So why people want to be around us?
Hold on one second
Yeah
You guys pick it on poor thing
I just you know
Yeah
I missed all of it. I just came back now
Yeah, no, no
I was just saying because thing was saying that he never talked badly about me because like Lisa said something and I said
No, I definitely saw it with my own eyes and use he said it in my heart
But it wasn't that bad for me to be like oh my god
But I was like it was hurtful because I thought you know things actually like
I don't think he meant it. I think he was just going through stuff and upset, but it doesn't mean it's not gonna make her break it
That means which in Spanish I think thing that is is cool. I think Arthur's the fact
Once we all realize that
Yeah, absolutely he always does
Bender need both bitch. I like you asshole. Well, I'm still here nigga
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
You guys are fucking
Go watch psycho cake nigga, that's another rule doctor nigga. Yeah, the rule doc is over there go watch cake. Yeah. Yeah, what?
How's he saying does anyone understand I'm tired of defending people
Everybody I'm just letting them punch it out. I'm not fine. Nobody's fighting over me. They're fighting with each other
I swear to God. I what am I supposed to do? I've been trying to hey
Fighting for you definitely
Everybody always blaming me though, it doesn't fucking matter though, oh my god.
I'm not part of the community, I'm in need of you.
You are in need of me.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
You always say that and I always, thank you for saying that to me for a year and always
tenoring me.
I love you.
I
Cryed about it
You don't have permission to restream me if you know I just was somebody told me backstage that you are restreaming me
You don't have permission to restream me, you know
Who's a little bitchy nark
Stop listening to me, Peter.
Who's telling her backstage things?
Christina's just awful.
She's just awful.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, but then, but then just to be spiteful,
she'll probably just keep it up and then like try to strike me
or something.
She's, she's struck me before, Kate.
She struck me before for some like pictures. I was already out there
Hmm
Good I want one left don't
Squiddy's gone. Hey, let me say egg. Well, do you want me to say egg?
Good here has syrup on it. I mean
Let's do it. Let's let's watch some more just like get the water get mad and stuff. I love it
We watch some more beta
They're totally harassing thing that is
Sam and speaking on thing that is he's calling
Your salmon is called you and I doxers when it's like literally you've shown like public photos and stuff
I mean, it's so ridiculous
But kick
Okay, here I got it. I got it. Here we go
Thank you restart your channel restart it so we start your life because I didn't give you permission started all over again
Okay, I got me I don't know and the timestamp. Oh
Oh, my god. Be wise. Yeah, because I know
Never will go for anybody. Well, just restart it
Even if he privatizes it youtube still has access to okay. He put it back up. All right, so I'm just gonna give me a moment
I gotta go take care of something on my
I want him he doesn't listen hold on one second you guys